你们在看什么
What are you guys looking at?
是我演的一战电影的海报  你看
It's a poster for that WWI movie I'm in. Check it out.
看起来很暴力嘛
Wow! It looks really violent!
我知道  我即将在各大戏院露面
I know. I'm coming soon to a theater near you.
我经过THX认证  我不适宜儿童观看
I'm in THX. I'm unsuitable for children!
我等不及要看这部电影了
I cannot wait to see this.
已经有传闻说它能拿奥斯卡了
Yeah, yeah. It's generating Oscar buzz.
是我先说的  我还以为是我
I started that!  I thought I did!
我刚刚跟经纪人谈过...
Guess what? I just talked to my agent...
下星期有首映会  你们通通被邀请了
...and the premiere is next week and you're all invited!
我们要坐加长豪华轿车吗  当然
Will we take a limo?  Sure! Why not?
不去参加葬礼还能坐加长车  简直太棒了
I love taking limos when nobody died.
我显然没办法去了
Well, obviously I won't be able to come.
那些还没查过日历的人听好了
For those who haven't checked their calendars,
今天是我的预产期
today's my due date.
我想借这个机会谢谢大家
I just want take a moment and thank you guys
在我怀孕期间一直这么照顾我
for how great you've been during this time.
没有你们我绝对办不到
I really couldn't have done it without you.
过去的九个月我很开心
I loved these last 9 months.
虽说我很期待进入下一阶段...
Even though I'm looking forward to the next part...
我会很怀念怀孕的这段时光
...I am really gonna miss being pregnant.
没错  我还是没生
That's right. Still no baby.
拜托  给我腾点地方坐
Come on, people, make some room.
亲爱的  或许你坐在这里会比较舒服
Sweetie, maybe you'd be more comfortable here.
你
You.
你对我做的孽还不够多吗
Like you haven't done enough.
我知道你现在很痛苦
I know how miserable you are.
我真的希望能帮上忙
I wish there was something I could do.
我希望自己是海马
I wish I were a sea horse.
因为是公海马负责孵育小宝宝
Because with sea horses, it's the male. They carry the babies.
而且我还会生活在海里  离你远远的
And then also, I'd be far away in the sea.
天啊
God.
我这辈子从来没有这么难受过
I have never been so uncomfortable in my entire life.
我了解  我也有过这种经历  我记得最后
I know. I've been there. I remember toward the end...
菲比  你的故事很精彩
Phoebe, that's a great story.
能不能帮我拿杯冰茶来再说
Can you tell it to me when you're getting me some iced tea?
天啊  滚出来  滚出来  滚出来
Oh, God, get out! Get out, get out, get out!
咱们滚吧
Let's.
《老友记》  第八季  第22集  瑞秋迟迟生不出
你生完宝宝了吗
Hey, did you have the baby yet?
你想让我过去坐在你身上吗
Do you want me to come over there and sit on you?
我真做得出来
Because I'll do it.
你怎么这么早就回来了
What are you doing here so early?
公司要我回家
They sent me home from work.
他们让我从现在就开始休产假  回家休息
They said, "Start your maternity leave now. Just rest."
为宝宝出生做好准备  去他们的
Get ready for the baby. You know what? Screw them!
如果他们不要我待在公司
If they don't want me there,
我就跟你们待在一起
I'll hang out with you guys.
或许你可以去做义工
Or you could do volunteer work.
喂  乔伊  我是艾丝特尔
Hello?  Joey, it's Estelle.
好消息  我帮搞你到了首映会的门票
Great news. I was able to get you
你可以带一位朋友出席
and one guest tickets to your premiere.
一位朋友  你之前说我可以拿到六张票
One guess? You told me I could have six tickets.
我把其中四张拿去易趣网拍卖了
Well, I sold four of them on eBay.
你会坐在"帅哥372"旁边
You'll be sitting next to HotGuy372.
天啊  难道我就只能带一个朋友去吗
Oh, my god. So that's it? I only get to bring one guest?
对  你什么时候来接我
Yeah. What time you wanna pick me up?
喂
Hello?
你们听到了吗
You hear that?
我只能带一个朋友参加首映会
I only get one extra ticket to my premiere.
所以我得在你们三个跟罗斯之间做选择
So somehow I have to pick between you three and Ross.
我呢  你说过你不想去
What about me?  You said you didn't want to go.
没错  但我还是希望有被重视的感觉
I don't. But I would still like to be acknowledged.
难道我怀孕了就变成隐形人了吗
Because I'm pregnant, I'm invisible?
你绝不是隐形人
Definitely not invisible.
罗斯根本不在这里  所以他出局了
Ross didn't care enough to be here, so I think he's out.
你打磕睡  你就输了
You snooze, you lose.
他没有打磕睡  他在教书
He's not snoozing. He's teaching a class.
那么一定有人在打磕睡
Well, then somebody's snoozing.
乔伊  不要因为我的话影响你的选择
And, Joey, not that this should affect you at all,
但如果你选了我...
but if you pick me...
我打算穿露到这里的紧身连衣裙
...I was planning on wearing a sequin dress cut down to here.
我还没有看过这套连衣裙
I haven't seen this dress.
穿上绝对有影星风范
Star in a movie.
乔伊  你想挑谁都可以
Joey, you pick whoever you want.
听从你内心的声音
Listen to your heart.
它跟你说了什么
What does it tell you?
菲比  菲比  菲比...
Phoebe. Phoebe. Phoebe.
这个嘛...
Well...
我想我要挑钱德勒
I think I want to take Chandler.
菲比  菲比  菲比...
Phoebe, Phoebe, Phoebe.
你想带我去吗
You want to take me?
对  我希望能带大家一起去
Yeah, I'm sorry. I wish I could take everybody.
但钱德勒一直都很支持我的工作
But Chandler's always supported my career.
他帮我付表演课跟大头照等等的费用
He's paid for acting classes, headshots and stuff.
这就是我回报你的方式
This will be my way of paying you back.
所以你不打算还我钱了吗
So you're never actually going to pay me back?
只因为他帮你付大头照的钱  你就要选他
Just because he paid for your headshots, you're gonna take him?
你大概还没搞明白那件连衣裙有多露
I don't think you're comprehending just how slutty this dress is.
不仅是因为他帮我付了钱
It's not just the stuff he paid for.
他真的很支持我  你们知道吗
It's everything, you know?
他跟我对台词
He read lines with me.
我紧张的时候  他陪我去试镜
He went with me on auditions when I was nervous.
我没拿到我想要的角色时  他会安慰我
Then he consoled me after I didn't get parts that I really wanted.
你一直很相信我
You always believed in me, man,
即使连我都不相信自己
even when I didn't believe in myself.
我一直都知道你会成功
I always knew you were gonna make it.
我非常以你为荣
I'm so proud of you.
谢谢  那对我来说很重要
Thanks, that means a lot to me.
莫妮卡  或许他们之中有人想穿你的连衣裙
Mon, maybe one of these guys wants to wear your dress.
我得去刮胡子
I'm gonna go shave.
对  我得去吐痰了
Yeah, well, I'm gonna go spit.
我得去尿尿了
I have to pee.
如果五分钟后我还没出来
If I don't come out in five minutes,
那肯定是因为我被百花香味给熏死了
it's because I've choked to death on the potpourri stink.
等她出来以后  你捏住她的鼻子
When she comes out, you hold her nose,
我对她的嘴巴吹气  宝宝就会掉出来
I'll blow in her mouth and the kid'll just... right out of her.
她都晚了一周了  今天她一定会生
She's over a week late. She's got to have it today, right?
我不知道  我觉得应该还要一阵子
I don't know. I think it's still gonna be a while.
你想加点刺激吗
Care to make it interesting?
我跟你打赌  她明天这个时候就会生
I bet you she'll have it by this time tomorrow.
没问题
You're on.
好吧  赌多少  我跟你赌十万块
Okay, how much?  One hundred thousand dollars.
50块如何
How about 50 bucks?
好吧  我会打电话让苏黎世银行汇点钱过来
Fine, I'll call Zurich and move some money around.
好了  这次轮到谁来扶我起来了
All right, whose turn is it to help me get up?
家里没人
No one's here.
该死
Oh, damn it!
这简直是太刺激  太迷人了
This is so exciting. So glamorous!
好多人帮我们拍照  我看起来如何
People taking our picture. How do I look?
太高了一点  什么
A little tall.  What?
你能不能蹲低一点  让我看起来高一点
Would you crouch down a bit so that I look taller?
很好
There you go.
简直太刺激了
It's just so glamorous.
莫妮卡  瑞秋来了
Oh, hey, Mon? Rach is here.
你还没生
And you're still pregnant.
真对不起  我知道你很不舒服
I'm sorry. I know how uncomfortable you are.
你知道吗  你看起来棒极了
You know what? You look great.
就跟50块钞票一样
Yeah, like 50 bucks.
我得去尿尿
I have to go pee.
很明显  这个宝宝把我的膀腕当成玩具捏
Apparently this baby thinks my bladder is a squeeze toy.
该死  50块拿去
Damn it. Here's your 50 bucks.
你竟然会输  这真是太有趣了
That's interesting that you lost.
我记不得了  你喜欢输吗
Now, I forget, do you like to lose?
好吧  别说了
All right, stop it.
我们加倍赌她明天会生  好  跟你赌
Double or nothing she has it by tomorrow.  Fine, you're on.
在那之前  葛兰特将军
Until then, General Grant,
你就在这里安心扎营吧
why don't you set up camp... right there?
瑞秋在这里吗  我们得去看医生
Is Rachel here? We have a doctor's appointment.
她在厕所里
She's in the bathroom.
瑞秋  我们得走了  马上好
Rach, we gotta go.  In a minute!
大家问我们为什么没在一起
People ask me why we're not together.
我都不知道该怎么告诉他们
I just don't know what to tell them.
好吧  我们走吧
All right, all right, let's go.
你要不要先去换衣服
Do you want to go change first?
医生会等我们  但如果你快一点的话...
The doctor's staying open late for us, but if you hurry...
不用  我这样很好
No, I'm fine.
你不觉穿这套衣服有点不合适吗
You don't think that's a little inappropriate?
什么  天啊  别火上浇油了
What?  Good God, man. Don't anger it.
罗斯  现在外面有38度高温
Ross, it is 100 degrees outside.
这是好几个星期以来我第一次...
For the first time in weeks, I am...
好吧  随便你
Fine. Whatever you want.
你是妈咪
You're the mommy.
可别叫我"妈眯"
No! Don't call me "Mommy."
你那么称呼你妈就已经够受了
It's bad enough you call your own mother that.
这一次我同意她的说法
I'm actually with her on this one.
我还以为自己知道敌人是谁  但敌人却是你
I thought I knew who the enemy was, but it was you all along.
好了  我的打斗戏要开始了
Okay, this is it. This is my big fight scene coming up.
我要为第82地面师的每位弟兄奋战
I'm fighting for every man in the 82nd Ground Division.
罗斯  我能问你一件事吗
Ross? Can I ask you something?
卡罗尔怀本的时候...
When Carol was pregnant with Ben...
你有这么暴躁吗
...were you this irritating?
你说什么  没事  你只是...
Excuse me?  Nothing. You're just...
你最近对我很不耐烦
You've been a little short with me lately.
我无意惹毛你
I'm not trying to irritate you.
那么你一定是有惹毛我的天份
Well, then, you must have a natural talent for it.
医生马上就要过来了
You know what? The doctor will be in soon.
我们在那之前还是别说话了吧
Why don't we not speak until then?
好吧
Okay.
呼吸声再大一点   罗斯  感觉真好
Seriously. Breathe louder, Ross. That's great.
我们应该问医生她知不知道...
We should ask the doctor if she even knows...
怎么接生半人半魔的孩子
...how to deliver a baby that's half human, half pure evil!
朗医生  你好吗
Hi, Dr. Long. How are you?
你对她倒很好
You're nice to her.
她手上有药
She has the drugs.
我帮你快速检查一下  好的
We'll do a quick check.  Okay.
已经迟了八天吗  对
So eight days late, huh?  Yeah.
你一定觉得很不舒服
You must be getting a little uncomfortable.
对  只有一点
Yeah, just a tad.
宫口已经扩张了八成  就快了
You're 80% effaced. So you're on your way.
但你可能还得等上一阵子
It still could last a while longer.
如果你很着急  有些方法可以促产
If you're anxious, there are ways to help things along.
那就赶紧的吧
Do them!
事实上你们可以自助
Actually, they're things that you can do.
在家里做治疗
Just some home remedies.
根据我的经验  我发现有些方法很有效
In my experience, I've found some are very effective.
我们愿意尝试任何方法
Well, we are ready to try anything.
好的  你可以喝一种药草茶
Okay. There's an herbal tea you can drink.
你可以喝蓖麻子油  吃辣的食物
You can take some castor oil. There's spicy foods.
我们全都愿意尝试
Great. We will do all of those.
长时间散步  很好  没问题
Taking a long walk.  Good. Done.
据证实  最有效的方法就是做爱
And there's the one that's proved most effective: Sex.
你一定是在开玩笑
You've got to be kidding me!
演得好  乔伊  太棒了  超一流
Good job, Joe! Well done! Topnotch!
你真的喜欢吗  当然喜欢
You liked it? You really liked it?  Oh, yeah!
你具体喜欢哪个部份
Well, which part exactly?
整部电影  我们走吧
The whole thing! Here we go!
不  说具体一点
No, no, no. Give me some specifics.
我就喜欢具体细节  细节处理得最棒了
I loved the specifics. The specifics were the best part.
有袋鼠出场的那场戏呢
Hey, what about the scene with the kangaroo?
你喜欢吗
Did you like that part?
看到一战的电影里出现袋鼠
I was surprised to see a kangaroo
我吓了一大跳
in a World War I epic.
你睡着了
You fell asleep!
电影里面根本没有袋鼠
There was no kangaroo!
我的建议他们一条都没采纳
They didn't take any of my suggestions!
谢谢你来捧场  回头见
Thanks a lot for coming. See you later.
别走  我很抱歉
Don't go. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
看  这家伙睡着了
Look, this guy fell asleep!
他也睡着了  生他的气啊
He fell asleep too! Be mad at him!
或是叫救护车来
Or call an ambulance!
医生说什么
What did the doctor say?
知道宝宝何时会出生吗
Any news on when the baby will come?
不知道  她教了我们一些促产的方法
No. She gave us ideas on how to induce labor.
我们都试过了
We tried them all.
我们去散了步  喝了茶
We went for a walk, we tried special tea,
吃蓖麻子油跟辣的食物  全都没用
castor oil, spicy food. Nothing has worked.
有个方法我们没试
There is one thing we didn't try.
但某人觉得那会惹来大麻烦
But someone thinks that that will open up a can of worms.
什么方法
What is it? What is it?
如果有办法让宝宝今天就出生
If it's gonna help bring the baby here, today...
我觉得你们应该试试看
I mean, I think you should do it.
我们得做爱  那就做啊
It's sex.  Do it!
莫妮卡  你们很久没做爱了
Monica.  It's been a really long time for you.
我是说女人也有需要
I mean, women have needs.
快去吧  满足你的需要
Do it. Get yours.
这种事我可说不好
Oh, I don't know about that.
我觉得如果你们两个做了爱
I think if the two of you had sex,
那浮动诊胎法一定会出大问题
the repercussions would be catastrophic.
好吧  我们实际一点
All right, let's be practical.
如果罗斯不愿意
If Ross isn't willing to do it,
这世上不只有他能跟你做爱
he's not the only guy in the world you can have sex with.
你可以借用钱德勒  钱德勒很厉害
You could borrow Chandler. Chandler is good.
莫妮卡  你这是怎么了
Monica, what is the matter with you?
没什么  我只是希望宝宝能在今天出生
Nothing. I just want the baby to be born today.
为什么一定要是今天
Why? Why today?
好吧
Okay, fine.
我一直在跟菲比打赌你会生
I keep betting Phoebe that you're gonna have the baby,
我不想再输钱了
and I don't want to lose again.
什么  她这么痛苦
What? While she's been going through this hell,
你们却在赌钱
you've been making money?
你们拿朋友持续经受痛苦来当赌注
You're betting on your friend staying in this misery?
我也要赌  什么
I'll take that bet.  What?
我已经够惨了  还不如找点钱赚
I'm miserable here. I may as well make some money out of it.
我也可以加入吗
Can I get some of that action?
等等  现在变成我跟你们三个对赌
Wait a minute. I'm betting against all of you?
别担心  我真的觉得明天就要生了
Don't worry. I really do feel like tomorrow it's gonna happen.
好吧
Okay.
嘿  睡美人
Hey, Sleeping Beauty.
你跑到哪里去了  打电话都不接
Where have you been? I try to call you.
我想跟你谈谈  我还是觉得很过意不去
I want to talk to you. I still feel bad.
不是吧  你不开心了吗  睡不着觉了吗
Oh, no. Were you upset? Did you lose sleep?
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我之所以过来解决我们之间的问题
The reason I came over is to settle things between us.
是因为你帮了我很多忙
You've done a lot for me in my career.
我想请你去看首映会来报答你
I wanted to pay you back by taking you to the premiere,
但你却睡着了
but you missed it.
我欠你多少钱  什么
So how much do I owe you?  What?
给我个数字  我不想欠你
Give me a number. I don't want to owe you anything.
你什么都不欠我
You don't owe me anything.
我不要你的...  说还就还
I don't want your...  We're doing this!
你帮我付第一次大头照的费用多少钱
You got me my first headshots. How much were those?
我不知道  五百块
I don't know, $500.
好吧  五百块  还有呢
Okay, $500. What else?
还有第二组大头照
Then there was the second set.
恶评如潮的"鼻涕虫"大头照
The infamous "booger" headshots.
好吧  再加五百块
Okay, so that's another $500.
五百加五百是...
That's 500 and 500. That's...
你需要计算器吗  谢谢
You want a calculator?  Please.
拿去
Here.
好吧  还有呢
All right, what else?
还有表演课  舞台打斗课  踢踏舞课
Well, there's acting classes, stagecombat classes, tap classes...
这些天知地知  你知我知就好
Which we're still keeping under our hats.
我还付钱请教练
Then there was that dialect coach who helped you with that play
教你说南方腔
where you needed a southern accent.
上了20小时的课后  你还是满口牙买加腔
Which, after 20 hours of lessons, still came out Jamaican.
你在胡说什么
What the hell are you talking about?
"南方将会再起  兄弟"
The South will rise again, man.
对  那笔钱花得很值得
Yes, money wellspent.
好吧  还有呢  房租
Okay, what else? Rent.
两三年的房租  水电费  伙食费
Okay. Two, three years of rent, utilities, food...
好吧 我写张支票给你
Okay, so I'm writing you a check for...
你不就是看我电影的时候睡着了嘛
So you fell asleep during my movie.
没什么大不了的  对吧
Big deal, right?
这玩意要怎么清除
How do you clear this thing?
把你的墨西哥卷吃掉
Come on. Finish your enchilada.
罗斯  我们试过所有的辛辣食品  根本没用
Ross, we've tried all the spicy food. It's not working.
好吧  拿去  吃根辣椒
Okay, here, have one of these peppers.
天啊  好辣  我的天啊
Oh, God. So hot. Oh, my God.
对了  拿过辣椒之后
By the way, you don't want to touch the pepper
别用手摸眼睛
and then touch your eye.
我什么感觉都没有
I am feeling nothing.
说到辣  看到你现在的样子
Speaking of hot, watching you do that...
让我很想跟你做爱
...really makes me want to have sex with you.
别闹了
Stop it.
来嘛  罗斯  我们为什么要浪费时间
Come on, Ross! Why are we wasting time with all this other stuff?
明知道这招很管用
We know it's gonna work.
这是医生的建议
It's doctorrecommended.
抱歉  但我们总该有点分寸
I'm sorry. But we have to have some boundaries.
天啊  我快辣死了
My God, I'm dying.
来嘛  罗斯
Come on, Ross.
我们以前都做过  再做一次又怎样
We've done it before. We'll do it again.
这也算是给我的怀孕期画上圆满句号了
It'll be a nice way to bookend the pregnancy.
这太疯狂了  我不会因为要让你生孩子
This is insane. I'm not gonna make love to you
就跟你做爱
just so you'll go into labor.
做爱  你是娘娘腔吗
Make love? What are you, a girl?
想让男人脱裤子  说这种话最管用了
Always a great way to get into a man's pants.
你就当是在提供服务
You'll be performing a service, okay?
把我当成一罐番茄酱
Think of me as a ketchup bottle.
有时候你得敲敲瓶底才能把番茄酱倒出来
Sometimes, you have to bang on the end of it to get it to come out.
我喜欢你满嘴淫话的样子
I love when you talk dirty to me.
我知道  你说得对  那样一点都不性感
I know it. You're right. That's not sexy.
我把叉子给掉了
Oh, I seem to have dropped my fork.
我得弯下腰去捡
Let me just bend over and get it.
天啊
Oh, God!
好吧  够了  我是不会跟你做的
Okay, enough. This is not going to happen.
来吧  罗斯  我真的很难受
Come on, Ross. I'm miserable here.
来吧  这是你惹出来的事  你得负责到底
Come on, you started this, now you finish it!
来吧  懦夫  跟我做爱吧
Come on, wuss. Make love to me.
你知道吗  什么
You know what?  What?
算了
Forget it.
怎么了  罗斯  你不想谈吗
What now, Ross, you're not gonna talk?
你到底要惹我惹到什么时候
How on earth will you ever annoy me?
等一下  我知道了
Oh, wait a minute, I know.
你以为吃点辣椒
I mean you'd think the damn jalepeno
就能治好你的鼻窦炎吗  才不会呢
would've cleared up your sinuses, but no!
那可不够...你在干什么
That's not enough... What are you doing?
我要让你把宝宝生出来
I'm getting that baby out of you!
天啊  我知道
Oh, God!  I know.
不
Oh, no, no, no.
我觉得我的羊水破了
I think my water just broke.
我太厉害了
I am good!
好吧  我拿了枕头还有包包
Okay, I got the pillow. I got the bag.
你拿了钥匙吗  我拿了
You got the keys?  I got the keys.
我们的宝宝要出生了
We're having a baby.
我还来不及看书上的这个章节
I didn't have time to read this part of the books,
但你觉得我们还有时间...
but do you think we have time...?
来不及了  好吧  我们走吧
Not so much.  Okay, let's go.
200  谢谢
200.  Thank you.
就这样吧  我不在乎宝宝何时出生
That's it. I'm done. I don't care when the baby comes.
我不想再赌了
No more betting.
好吧
Okay.
喂
Hello?
好
Okay.
我们再赌一次也无妨
I guess we could bet one more time.
瑞秋要生了吗  你怎么知道
Is Rachel having the baby?  How did you know that?
乔伊  钱德勒  时间到了
Joey! Chandler! It's time.
他们在咖啡厅
They're at the coffee house.
你什么都知道
You know everything!
等一下  我跟你赌宝宝超过七磅重
Wait, double or nothing. I bet you the baby is over 7 pounds.
我跟你赌宝宝有头发  我跟你赌是女儿
I bet you it has hair! I bet you it's a girl.
我们知道她要生女儿
We know it's a girl.
我给你很高的赔率
I'll give you really good odds.